<resources>
    <string name="education_title">Resources</string>

    <!--    Strings for article names and info-->
    <string name="section_title_text_1">Farmers Markets</string>

    <string name="title_text_1">National Farmers Market Directory</string>
    <string name="body_text_1">The Farmers Market Directory provides convenient access to information about local produce including: local farms, market locations, directions, operating times, product offerings, accepted forms of payment, and more.</string>

    <string name="title_text_2">Local Harvest - Farmers Market</string>
    <string name="body_text_2">Real Food, Real Farmers, Real Community. Lists local farms, farmers markets, restaurants, and other produce related events.</string>

    <string name="section_title_text_2">Government Nutrition Programs</string>

    <string name="title_text_3">Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program (SNAP)</string>
    <string name="body_text_3">Discover how SNAP provides nutrition benefits to supplement the food budget of low-income families so they can purchase healthy food and move towards self-sufficiency.</string>

    <string name="title_text_4">SNAP for Women, Infants, and Children (WIC)</string>
    <string name="body_text_4">Learn about supplemental SNAP benefits for pregnant women, infants, and children under the age of five.</string>

    <string name="title_text_5">Seniors Farmers’ Market Nutrition Program (SFMNP)</string>
    <string name="body_text_5">SFMNP provides support for low-income seniors in accessing local, fresh food.</string>

    <string name="title_text_6">Google Find Food Support</string>
    <string name="body_text_6">Find food resources like food pantries, snap benefits, and stores that accept EBT with Google’s Find Food Support.</string>

    <string name="section_title_text_3">Healthy Eating</string>

    <string name="title_text_7">USDA - Healthy Eating</string>
    <string name="body_text_7">Get resources to help you eat a healthy diet with vegetables, fruits, protein, grains, and dairy foods.</string>

    <string name="title_text_8">American Heart Association - Healthy Eating</string>
    <string name="body_text_8">Learn what to look for at the grocery store, restaurants, your workplace, and any eating occasion.</string>

    <string name="section_title_text_4">Communities</string>

    <string name="title_text_9">Community Fridge Locations</string>
    <string name="body_text_9">Find a community fridge near you!</string>

    <string name="title_text_10">The Black Church Food Security Network</string>
    <string name="body_text_10">The Black Church Food Security Network (BCFSN) utilizes an asset- based approach in organizing and linking the vast resources of historically African american congregations in rural and urban communities.</string>

    <string name="title_text_11">Black Farmers’ Network</string>
    <string name="body_text_11">Black Farmers’ Network (BFN) is a site for rural, African-American farmers to share stories, products and services in a now digital-driven economy.</string>

    <!--    Probably can delete all of this stuff?-->
    <string name="app_name">edu resources attempt</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">Harvest4Us</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

</resources>